# **Arkadiusz Sarach**

# Junior Front-End Developer



### **Personal Info**

### **Email**

arkadiusz.sarach@gmail.com

#### **Address**

Cracow

#### **GitHub**

https://github.com/Ajek1993

#### LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/arkadiusz-sarach/

#### Website

https://my-portoflio-mu.vercel.app/

#### **Skills**

Programming languages: JavaScript (Node.js), Typescript, CSS, SCSS

Frameworks/Libraries: React, Next.js, Tailwind CSS, Material UI, NextUI, Express.js

IDE: Visual Studio Code

Other: Git, Firebase, MongoDB, ESLint, Postman

# Languages

English - B2

# **Hobby/Interest**

music (playing drums), literature (Sapkowski, Cejrowski, astronomy), sport (cycling), computer games Determined to change the industry to IT, I am constantly willing to develop and acquire new knowledge. I quickly learn technical issues and can effectively apply them in practice. Since I started learning, I have experienced great satisfaction from discovering new possibilities offered by the latest libraries and frameworks. This is an additional motivation for me to improve in this field. The most inspiring projects for me are those that make use of the potential of the latest technologies. I am particularly fascinated by creating working algorithms that solve problems.

# **Projects**

### **Facebook Copy**

https://github.com/Ajek1993/facebook-copy

The application is similar to well-known social network (still in progress).
Technologies: Next.js, Typescript, TailwindCSS, Next UI, Firebase, Firestore, ESlint, OpenAI, git

#### **Fleet Manager**

https://github.com/Ajek1993/Fleet\_Manager

Web aplication to manage car's fleet - allows adding/removing cars, repairs, fuel, counting costs. Technologies: React, Material UI, Firebase, Firestore, git

### **Oddaj Rzeczy**

https://github.com/Ajek1993/OddajRzeczy

Node.js for programmers

**Branch supervisor** 

One page site - allows sending forms to data base.

Technologies: Next.js, Tailwind CSS, Firebase, Firestore, git

# **Education**

2023-12

- 2024-02	Coders Lab - Szkoła IT  Duration - 130 hours
2023-03	Front-End-Developer
- 2023-10	Coders Lab - Szkoła IT
	Duration - 180 hours
2013-10 - 2018-10	Mining geomechanics and underground construction, Master of Science
	Akademia Górniczo-Hutnicza im. Stanisława Staszica, Kraków

# **Work History**

2019-07

- nresent

present	Stava S.A., Kraków
2017-04	Driver
- 2019-06	Abacus Sp. z o.o., Kraków
2015-07 - 2015-08	Intern
	Polska Grupa Górnicza - KWK "Piast-Ziemowit" - Ruch Piast, Bieruń

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie danych osobowych zawartych w niniejszym dokumenciedo realizacji procesu rekrutacji zgodnie z ustawą z dnia 10 maja 2018 roku o ochroniedanych osobowych (Dz. Ustaw z 2018, poz. 1000) oraz zgodnie z RozporządzeniemParlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) 2016/679 z dnia 27 kwietnia 2016 r. w sprawieochrony osób fizycznych w związku z przetwarzaniem danych osobowych i w sprawieswobodnego przepływu takich danych oraz uchylenia dyrektywy 95/46/WE (RODO).